&gt;&gt; Good morning.
&gt;&gt; 早上好
[ Applause ]
[掌声]
Welcome to What's New In tvOS?
欢迎来到 tvOS 的新性能板块
I'm Hans, and I'm an engineer on
我是 Hans  tvOS 团队的
the tvOS Team.
一名工程师
This morning, with my colleague
今天早上  我将和我的同事
Marshall, I'd like to talk to
Marshall 一起
you about some of the
和大家介绍一下
enhancements and new APIs in
tvOS 的优化和
tvOS.
新的 API
We're going to do this in two
我们的演讲将分为两部分
parts, beginning with updates on
首先我们将介绍 SDK 整体的
the overall SDK.
更新
We're going to take a look at
我们先会介绍系统层面的
system-wide improvements, and
改善
then narrow down to individual
接着我们将讲述一些
widgets.
个别的小工具
Then, Marshall will talk to you
之后 Marshall 会和你们介绍
about some of the new APIs
一些关于视图控制器方面的
around view controllers.
最新的 API
We have a lot of ground to
我们的内容很多
cover, so let's get started.
所以现在演讲开始
First, is ODR or On Demand
首先要讲的是 ODR
Resources.
也就是按需资源
For those of you, new to ODR, it
你们中的某些人对这个词可能比较陌生
allows your app to keep its
ODR 使你们的 app 在 App 商店中
resources in the App Store,
保存自己的资源
instead of including in the App
而不是被包含在
Bundle.
App Bundle 中
And then, your app can download
之后你的 app 可以在需要的时候
them as they become needed.
下载这些资源
This helps your app to download
它们可以使你的 app 下载速度更快
fast, launch quickly, while
安装快捷
still providing very
同时为用户
high-quality content to the
提供高质量的
users.
内容
And all of this, without taking
而这些操作
up a lot of local storage on the
在任何时候
customer's device at any given
都不会占用用户设备的
time.
本地存储
Last year, there was an upper
去年 App bundle 的
bound to your app bundle at 200
最大容量为
megabytes.
200MB
This helped your app to be very
这会使你的 app 变得很简洁
lean, and ultimately, your
最终 你的用户
customers were able to start
也可以更快速地
using your app that much sooner.
使用你的 app
But since then, we have received
但是自那之后
many requests that this limit be
也有很多人请求我们
increased.
提升这个最大值
So, in tvOS 10.2, we increased
所以在 tvOS 10.2 中  我们将最大值
this to over 20 times at 4
提升了 20 多倍至
gigabytes.
4G
So, if you have an existing
所以  如果你有一个项目
project that conformed to the
是根据我们过去的最大值所制作的
old limit, and you have some
而你又想在 App bundle 中
resources that you wish you
增加一些新的
could have included in the app
资源
bundle, the new limit will
那我们新的最大值
enable you to do that.
将为这一切提供可能
First, go to the Asset Catalog,
首先 前往 Asset Catalog
and select the resource that you
选择你想要
want to move back into the app
移回至 App bundle 中的
bundle.
资源
And at the bottom of attributes
在属性面板的底部
inspector, simply delete the
删除
tags.
标签
Now, this resource is bundled,
现在  这些资源被捆绑了
so at runtime, you can directly
所以运行时间内
access it without first having
你不需要先发出
to make the bundle resource
捆绑资源需求
request for it.
就可以直接使用这些资源
And of course, this increase
当然了  这个最大值的增长
does not come at the cost of
并不会占用
counting towards the rest of
你剩余的
your asset pack allowance, which
资产包限额
remains the same at 20
它们将会保持在
gigabytes.
20GB
So, now, the combined size of
所以  现在你的 App bundle
your app bundle and content can
和内容的总量
be up to 24 gigabytes.
将最多可以达到 24GB
And this is a lot of content.
而这个容量可以包含很多内容
And we believe it will help you
我们相信这会使
make your app's user experience
你们 app 的用户体验
even richer than before.
比以前更丰富
So, that's ODR in tvOS.
这就是 tvOS 中的 ODR
Next, we're thrilled to report
接下来  我要说一件振奋人心的事情
that beginning tvOS 11, RTL or
那就是 tvOS 11 将
right to left languages, are
完全支持 RTL
fully supported.
也就是从右至左的语言
So, if your app looked like this
所以  如果你的 app 在英语里是这个样子
in English, it will look like
那么在阿拉伯语中将是这个样子
this in Arabic, and like this in
在希伯来语中则是
Hebrew.
这个样子
In other words, your text will
换句话说  你的文本
flow right to left, and most of
将从右至左排列
your user interface will appear
而你大部分的用户界面
automatically mirrored.
将会自动反向
And if you're used to supporting
如果你在 iOS 或者 macOS 中
RTL in iOS or macOS, you'll be
已经习惯了 RTL
pleased to know that everything
那么你应该会很高兴
works the exact same way on tvOS
在 tvOS 中也有相同的
as well.
功能
But if you're not, we have a few
不过如果你并不适应这个 我们也有
recommendations.
相应的推荐
First, is to use based
首先是使用有基础的
internationalization.
国际化
Base internationalization
基础国际化
separates string localization
将文本本地化与
from UI layout, so while you're
UI 布局相分离
working on the UI, your
当你致力于 UI 时
localization expert can continue
本地化专家可以
to translate the strings without
继续翻译字符串
worrying about interfering with
而不必担心
the layout.
影响布局
And all new projects are created
所有通过基础国际化创作的
with base internationalization
新项目都会在默认情况下
turned on by default.
打开
So, if you're starting anew,
所以如果你正在开始一个新项目
you're already there.
你已经可以使用这个功能了
But if you have an existing
不过如果你已经有一个
project that has yet to take
还没有采用这个功能的项目
advantage of this, you can go to
你可以前往 Project Info
the Project Info, and check the
查看
Use Base Internationalization
Use Base Internationalization 的复选框
checkbox to start using it.
来使用该功能
Next, is to use Auto Layout.
接下来  就是使用自动布局
In particular, leading and
尤其是在创作约束时的
trailing attributes instead of
前段或后端属性
left or right when creating the
而不是
constraint.
左或右
This is so that when the system
当系统布局 UI 时
lays out the UI, it can infer
它可以根据
the appropriate left or right
目前的语言方向
directions based on the current
来推测
language direction.
是向左还向右
And finally, constantly test
最终在开发中
your layout during development.
不断测试布局
And to help you with this,
为了实现这个功能
there's an option in Scheme
在 Scheme Settings 中
Settings where you can
有一个选项
temporarily set the application
你可以暂时设置
language.
运用的语言
So, you can set it to Arabic,
如果你将其设置为阿拉伯语
Hebrew, or even right to left
希伯来语  甚至是从右至左的
pseudo language, which simply
虚构的语言
flips the direction without
它都可以在不改变源语言的情况下
changing the actual language.
改变方向
Now, RTL support is new in tvOS
RTL 支持对于 tvOS 来说
this year, but it has been
是今年新的技术
around for iOS and macOS for a
但是在 iOS 和 macOS 中
number of years.
却已经运用了好几年
And previous years' sessions
前几年的大会
have great guidelines and best
对于 tvOS 对其的运用
practices that now apply to
提供了很好的指导作用
tvOS.
和实践经验
So, we highly recommend that you
所以  我们强烈推荐你们来
check them out.
试一试
And of course, RTL support is
当然了  RTL 支持是
built into TVML.
建立在 TVML 中的
So, if you're using TVML
如果你在 app 中
templates in your app, you'll
使用 TVML 样板
get all the right behaviors for
你将免费获得所有的
free.
性能
So, that's RTL support in tvOS.
这就是 tvOS 中的 RTL 支持
Next, is Safe Area.
接下来  我们来讲讲 Safe Area
Many TVs use Overscan in some
很多电视在一些形状或形式中
shape or form, creating a
会使用 Over scan
situation where not all the
在这种情况下
pixels are displayed to the
用户不能看到所有的
user.
像素
So, in the past, we have
在过去
recommended that you manually
前面会建议你插入
compensate for this by insetting
视图内容
your view's content.
来进行手动的补偿
And the API to assist you was
而协助你完成这个的 API
UIScrollView.
则是 UI scroll View
overscanCompensationInsets.
Over scan Compensation Insets
This provided you with the
这些将为你提供
values that you can then plug
可以插入
into your view or view
你的视图或者
controller's configuration code.
视图控制器配置码的数值
tvOS 11 introduces a more,
tvOS 11 会引入一个
robust framework for you to make
更稳固的框架
sure your content is within the
来保证你的内容能够在更少的
Safe Area, with much less work.
工作量的情况下  还在安全以内
So, for example, some properties
比如说
are automatically updated for
有些性能已经
you.
自动为你更新
Your view's safeAreaInsets is
你视图的 safe Area Insets
updated as it moves in and out
在视图层级中移动的过程里
of the view hierarchy.
自动更新了
And your view's safeLayoutGuide
而随着 Safe Area Inset 的变化
is also updated as the Safe Area
你视图中的 safe Layout Guide
Inset changes.
也自动更新了
But you can also customize your
但是你还是可以
own things, by using UIView
通过使用 UI View Controller 的
Controller's
Additional Safe Area Insets
additionalSafeAreaInsets.
进行自定义操作
And the values you specify here,
在计算 View Controller 的视图时
will be added when calculating
你在这里列举的数值
the Safe Area Insets of the View
也将被
Controller's view.
计算在内
Now when you link your app
现在如果你将自己的 app
against tvOS 11, your app will
链接到 tvOS11 中
be subject to the new behavior.
你的 app 将受新性能支配
And we highly recommend that you
我们建议大家抓住机会
take opportunity to audit your
检查自己的 app
app, and adjust the layout in
并根据这些新的 API
the context of these new APIs.
进行布局的调整
There was a session yesterday,
昨天有一个会议主题是
Updating Your App for iOS 11,
为 iOS 11 更新你的 app
that goes into this very topic
那个会议对这个话题
in depth.
进行了深入的分析
So, we recommend you check it
所以我建议各位
out.
可以去看一看
But if you have a view or view
不过如果你已经有一个
controller that manually
可以自动补偿 Overscan 的
compensates for Overscan, and it
视图或者视图控制器
does so in a rather delicate
而它们在这方面的运行又很良好
way, and you're hesitant to
如果你还在
touch it just yet, you can opt
犹豫  你可以
out of the new behavior on the
在视图或视图控制器基础中
view or view controller basis.
运用这些新性能
And to do this, there are Insets
要达到这一功效
Layout Margins from Safe Area
只需要在视图中
for your view, and view respects
输入 Insets Layout Margins from Safe Area
system minimum layout margins
在视图控制器中输入
for your view controller.
view respects system minimum layout margins
And our own experience suggests
根据我们的经验
that oftentimes, it's your
一般来说
scroll view that requires some
滚动视图需要
of your attention.
多加注意
So, for scroll views, there is
对于滚动视图
Content Inset Adjustment
我们有
Behavior.
Content Inset Adjustment Behavior
And by setting this to Never,
通过把这个设置为 “Never”
you're effectively opting out
你可以有效地
your scroll view to the new
将你的滚动视图
behavior.
取消新性能
So, that's Safe Area.
这就是 Safe Area
Next, is updating your app's
接下来我们来讲讲
data in the background.
如何在后台更新你的 app 数据
Last year, we brought user
去年
notification framework to the
我们为 tvOS 采用了
tvOS, so you can send remote or
用户通知框架
push notifications to your app.
你可以发送远程或推送通知你的 app
But there was one notable
但是有一个值得注意的
aspect.
方面
When the system received
如果你的 app 没有运行
multiple notifications while
而系统又收到了多条通知
your app is not running, it only
那么只有当用户
delivered the very last one and
明确地启动了你的 app 时
that, when the app is explicitly
系统才会发送
launched by the user.
最新的一条通知
And this is improving.
我们对这点进行了改善
In tvOS 11, when a notification
在 tvOS 11 中
is received by the system, the
如果系统收到了一个通知
system wakes your app in the
系统将在后台唤醒你的 app
background, and delivers it.
并传送这个通知
And this provides an effective
这就是进行
means for what's called a silent
无声通知的
notification.
一种有效的方法
A silent notification is a
无声通知指的是
notification that wakes up your
一个能在后台将 app 唤醒
app in the background, so it can
并且可以为用户
do some work transparently for
透明地做一些任务的
the user.
通知
That's where the word "silent"
这就是“无声”的
comes from.
来源
And by using silent
通过使用无声通知
notification, you can
你可以定期
periodically download new
下载新内容
content, refresh your app's
更新 app 数据
data, or even set up to alert
或者在 app 进入前台时
the user in the app, when the
设置成
app enters foreground.
可提醒用户
So, to configure your app to
因此，如果要将你的 app
process silent notification,
设置成无声通知
first, add remote notifications
首先要添加
background mode.
远程通知后台模式
And then, make your app
然后将你的 app
delegate, the user notification
设置为 delegate
center delegate.
user notification center delegate
And register to receive remote
同时 register 为
notifications.
接受远程通知
center did receive with
中心接收
completion handler, do the work.
completion handler 任务 完成工作
So, that's silent notifications.
这些通知是无声的
The second way of updating your
第二个在后台更新 app 数据的
app's data in the background is
方法就是
through a mechanism called
通过一个叫 Background Fetch 的
Background Fetch.
算法
So, if your app needs to for
比如说
example, periodically check for
你的 app 需要定期检查
new content, it can register for
新内容  它就可以
Background Fetch.
注册 Background Fetch
Then the system, when it deems
之后系统如果认为
an opportunity arises for you,
有个适合你的机会出现了
wakes it up in the background.
就会在后台将 app 唤醒
Your app can then initiate a
你的 app 就会发起一个
fetch operation and do the work.
提取操作并完成相应指令
To configure your app to do a
要将你的 app 设置
Background Fetch, first add
Background Fetch 首先需要
Background Fetch Background
添加  Background Fetch 后台模式
Mode, and then, in your app
其次  在 app 授权中
delegate, register for
注册
Background Fetch.
Background Fetch
And finally, in your application
最后  在应用设置中
perform Fetch with Completion
输入 “perform Fetch with Completion
Handler, implement the work, and
Handler” 的指令  开始执行任务
don't forget to call the
之后别忘了
Completion Handler with the
在获取结果的时候
fetch result.
输入 Completion Handler
So, that's Background Fetch.
这就是 Background Fetch
And as you can see, tvOS11
正如你所见
provides two new ways of
tvOS 11 在更新 app 数据方面
updating your app's data.
提供了两种新的方法
Often, you know exactly when new
一般来说  你都可以准确地知道
data is available for your app,
什么时候有适用于你的 app 的新数据
and that's when you call silent
这就是所谓的
notification.
无声通知
On the other hand, it's the
另一方面
system that knows, "When is the
系统也会了解
best time to check for updates
更新你的 app 的
for your app?"
最佳时机
And this is because it not only
这是因为它不仅
looks into its own resource
会观察自身资源的
availability, but also takes
可用性
into account user behaviors such
还会考虑用户行为
as which apps the user has been
比如用户使用最频繁的
using most frequently.
是什么 app
So, to take advantage of that,
所以  要想好好利用这个功能
register for Background Fetch.
注册 Background Fetch
And we hope you take advantage
我们希望各位能好好利用
of these new ways to make sure
这些新方法
your app is up to date, even
让你们的 app 即便在进入前台之前
before it enters the foreground.
也可保持最新状态
So, that's Background Update.
这就是后台更新
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
Next, is scrolling.
接下来  我要介绍“滚动”
When a scroll view has a large
如果一个滚动视图
amount of content, it is often
拥有大量内容
tedious, if not frustrating, to
那么要想将其全部翻阅完
scroll through them all, to get
并找到你想要的东西
to the exact item you want.
其实是非常繁杂的
So, in tvOS 10.2, we introduced
因此  在 tvOS 10.2 中
Accelerated Scrolling to help
我们引用了“加速滚动”功能
users scroll more efficiently.
该功能可以帮助用户更有效率地滚动屏幕
To enter the accelerated
要想进入加速滚动模式
scrolling mode, all it takes is
只需要在触摸板上
a few large swipes in the same
进行相同方向的
direction on the touch pad.
几次大幅滑动
Additionally, the user can swipe
另外  用户可以
on the far-right edge of the
在触摸板的最右端
touch pad, to browse through the
进行滑动  以此来浏览
indices.
整个目录
And the good news for us
对于开发者来说有个好消息就是
developers, is that we don't
我们不需要
have to do any additional work
任何附加的工作
to get this new behavior.
就可以获得这个新性能
In fact, it's built into any
实际上  包括表格视图
scroll views, including table
集合视图在内的
views, or even collection views.
每一个滚动视图里都安装了这个功能
And this behavior is always on,
这个功能会一直开着
and you can't turn it off.
你无法将其关闭
But there are some things you
不过你可以做一些工作
can customize to make sure that
让你的滚动视图
your scroll view works well
在你的设计内
within your design.
运行良好
So, by default, the index bar
默认情况下
appears as you enter the
当你进入加速滚动模式时
accelerated scrolling mode.
就会出现指标栏
But you can completely hide this
但是你可以通过
by overriding the Index Display
将 Index Display Mode 改为 Hidden
Mode to Hidden.
来隐藏它
Also, the default scroll
另外  默认的
indicator style works really
滚动指示器
well because it adapts to the
运行地也很好
view controllers light or dark
因为它自调整视图控制器 不管是明亮
user interface style.
还是深色的用户界面风格
But if your design requires you
如果你的设计
to have an explicit style, you
要求拥有一个明确的风格
can override this to black or
你可以将其改为
white, and then do that.
黑色/白色
Additionally, you can customize
另外  你可以
the index titles for your table
使用两种
views by using the two data
数据来定制
[inaudible] methods.
自己表格视图的索引标题
First, to get the array of index
首先  要获得索引名称的
titles, and to get the index for
阵列  并为规定的索引名称
a given index title.
获得索引
Similarly, for collection view,
与此相似的  对集合视图来说
you can get the array of index
你可以获得索引名称的阵列
titles and get the index path
并在指定的索引名称中
for a given index title.
获得索引路径
So, that's updates in Scroll
这就是滚动视图的
View.
功能更新
Next, is a new button type,
接下来  我将介绍一个新的按钮类型
UIButtonTypePlain.
UI Button Type Plain
But before that, let's take a
不过在开始之前
look at the system button.
我们先看一看系统按钮
UIButtonTypeSystem provides
如果按钮是清晰的
interactive focus effect when
UI Button Type System 会提供
the button is in focus, and
交互式的聚焦效果
background blur when it isn't.
如果按钮不清晰  背景则模糊
The background blur, provides
当背景模糊时
the affordance of a button and
它将会提供按钮的可视线索
also, enhances the legibility of
同时也将增加标题的
the title.
可识别性
It is one of the most widely
这是 tvOS 中
used controls in tvOS, which is
使用最广泛的控件之一
perhaps why we have heard from
也许这也是为什么我们
many of you that you'd like to
经常听到很多人提过想要
customize this a little bit
对其进行自定义修改
more, to add a background color,
比如说
for example.
增加背景色
So, in tvOS 11, we're making a
所以在 tvOS 11 中 我们将
new button type,
制作一个新的按钮类型
UIButtonTypePlain.
UI Button Type Plain
A plain type button has all of
一个简单类型的按钮
the interactive focus effect of
拥有系统按钮拥有的
a system button, but without the
除了背景模糊之外的
background blur, which lends
所有交互性聚焦效果
itself to full customization.
这使其可以全定制
And using a plain type button is
使用简单类型的按钮
straightforward.
很容易
First, create the button with
首先  用 UI Button Type Plain
UIButtonTypePlain, and continue
创造按钮
customizing it.
接着对其进行定制
So, that's the plain type
这就是简单类型的
button.
按钮
Thank you.
谢谢
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
The last set of enhancements in
第一部分要讲的最后一个优化
this first part, is around
是关于
UIImageView.
UI Image View 的
On tvOS, interactive focus
在 tvOS 中
effect is an important
交互性聚焦特效是项重要的
technique.
技术
It gives your users a sense that
这会让你的用户感受到
they're connected with the
他们与屏幕相连
screen, and also tells them
同时也能告诉他们
exactly where their focus is.
自己的焦点在哪里
And most often, we use floating,
很多时候  我们会使用
layered images to maximize the
漂浮或者分层图像来将效果
effect.
最大化
Since it was first introduced,
在我们初次引进这个功能时
many of you have asked for a way
你们很多人都询问
to customize this further, by
要如何进一步将其自定义化
adding your own content at
通过在运行时增加你们自己的内容
runtime, so they can participate
这样它们就可以
in the focus effect.
采用聚焦特效
In tvOS 11, we're introducing an
在 tvOS 11中
easy and safe way to do that,
我们引进了一个简单安全的方法
and that's Image Overlay.
那就是 Image Overlay
Image Overlay uses a new
Image Overlay 使用了一个名为
property, Overlay Content View,
Overlay Content View 的新性能
which is similar in concept to
这个性能在概念上与
the content view in table view
图表视图或集合视图中的
or collection view cells, in
内容视图比较相似
that that's where you add your
在这里你将把你的内容作为
content as sub-views.
子视图进行添加
By default, overlay content view
在默认条件下  叠加内容视图将把
clips its child views to the
子视图添加到
image views bounds, but you can
image views 的 bounds 中
override this and draw outside
不过你可以将其推翻 并通过
of it, by setting the clips to
把 overlay content view 中的
bounds of the overlay content
clips to bounds 这一条目设置为 “false”
view to false.
来将其拖出
The next improvement in
另外一个 UI Image View 的优化
UIImageView is in Alpha Channel
就是 Alpha Channel
Support.
Support
As you know, layered image are
大家都知道  分层图像
required to have an opaque
需要拥有不透明的
background.
背景
And even floating -- flat single
即便是悬浮的—平面的单层图像
layered images, for floating
为了拥有悬浮效果
effect, they are also required
也需要拥有
to have an opaque background.
不透明的背景
In tvOS 11, that is no longer
在 tvOS 11中  情况就
the case.
不一样了
So, you can now have arbitrary
你们现在将拥有
shape alpha-channel, and for
不透明的 alpha-channel
some of you, this might scream
也许你们当中有些人
non-rectangular shadows.
想要非矩形阴影
So, instead of just talking
口说无凭
about this, I'd like to ask my
我想让我的同事 Paul
colleague Paul to show us in a
通过一个 demo 来向大家
demo.
展示
Paul?
Paul
[ Applause ]
[掌声]
&gt;&gt; So, yes, I'd like to demo
&gt;&gt; 好的  我会通过一个 demo
some of the new features of
来展示一下 tvOS 11中
UIImageView in tvOS 11.
UI Image View 的新特点
I've been working on this simple
我一直都致力于研究这个简单的
video playing app here.
视频播放 app
I liked they had a couple of new
我很喜欢这些
features.
新功能
The first thing I like to do, is
我想做的第一件事就是
add an icon to the poster to
在海报上增加一个图标
make it obvious that when you
让其变得更加明显
select the poster, the video
这样当你选择一个海报时
will start playing.
视频就会开始播放
And I also like to add a
我还想在我已经开始
progress bar, to the posters of
观看的视频的海报上
the videos that I've started
增加一个
watching.
进度栏
And that way, I can quickly see
这样  我就可以快速地
how far through the videos I am.
知道我看到了哪个位置
So, I'm just going to add some
所以  为了实现这个 UI
views to the image view of the
我要为海报的图像视图
poster to implement that UI.
增加一些视图
And you can see that the UI
诚如各位所见
shows up, but it feels pretty
UI 出现了  但是
disconnected from the image
它与后面移动的图像好像
that's moving behind it.
是相互分离的
And I'd really like for that UI
我希望让 UI
to move along with the image.
可以和图像一起移动
Luckily, that's easy to do in
幸运的是  在 tvOS 11中
tvOS 11.
这很简单
Instead of adding those views to
我可以直接把这些视图加入
my image view, I'm just going to
image view 中的 overlay content view 里
add them to the image view's
而不用加入
overlay content view.
我的 image view 中
Build and run and see how that
我们来看看最终的
looks.
效果
That's more like the effect I
这就是我想要的
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
Yes, the UI moves along with the
UI 可以和图像一起移动
image, as if it was another
就好比它已经成为分层图像中的
layer in the layered image.
一层了
And the next thing I'd like to
接下来
do is add some gadgets to these
我要为这些海报
posters, and that way I can mark
增加一些小玩意
videos that might be new or
这样我就可以为用户
otherwise interesting to the
标记一些新的或者有趣的
user.
视频
And I'm just going to add a
我将为这个 app
touch button to the app that
增加一个触摸按钮
will let me toggle those badges
这样我就能控制这些标记的开关
on and off so they can make sure
以此让 UI 根据我的
the UI's working the way I want.
想法来运行
To make that touch button, I'm
要制作触摸按钮
going to make a button of type
我首先要设置一个类型是自定义的
custom, so that I don't get
按钮  这样我就不必像
system chrome that you
你们一般设置按钮时那样
ordinarily get with a button.
配备一个系统浏览器
And I'm going to set the
之后我将把按钮的 image view
button's image view to adjust
设置为
image when ancestor focused, and
“当原型聚焦时  调整图像”
that way it'll get the nice,
完成这些操作后
floating effect when the button
当按钮对准时  就会产生
becomes focused.
良好的漂浮效果
And I'm going to use the same
我将会为按钮
image for the button that I'll
和实际的图标
use for the actual badges
使用相同的
themselves.
图像
And the badge image, has a
图标拥有
circular alpha channel.
循环式阿尔法通道
And in tvOS 11, that works well
在 tvOS 11 中
with the floating effect of the
阴影的悬浮效果以及
shadow and the spotlight and
聚光灯会让一切
work the way that you would
都按照你预期的想法
expect.
运行
When I tap the button, I'm going
当我轻触按钮时
to add the badge image to the
我将为那些海报的
overlay content view of these
overlay content view 增添
posters.
图标
We'll see how that looks.
我们来看看效果
We can see that there's a
我们会发现这里有一个
problem.
问题
The badge is there in the upper
图标在左上角
left corner, but it's being
但是它却夹在
clipped to the transformed frame
图像视图中变换的图像
of the image view.
里面
And often, that's exactly what
一般来说
you want for your overlays.
这就是大家想要的分层效果
In this case, it's not what I
但是这却不是
want.
我想要的
Luckily, I was listening to
幸运的是  我听了 Hans 的演讲
Hans' talk, and he let me know
他让我知道了
how to fix this.
如何将其修复
I'm just going to set clips to
我只需要在 overlay content view 中
bounce to false on the overlay
将 clips To Bounds 设置成 false
content view.
即可
Let's try that one more time.
我们再试一次
So, I'll toggle the badges on.
我把图标打开
That's what I was I hoping to
这就是我想要的
see.
效果
So, now the badges draw the way
现在图标的拖拽方式
I want them to.
就是我想要的
And then continue to move with
它们将与剩下的 UI
the image along with the rest of
和图像
the UI.
一起移动
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
So, that's just a quick look at
这就是关于 tvOS 11 中
some of the new features of
UI Image View 的新功能的
UIImageView in tvOS 11.
简单介绍
Back to you, Hans.
把时间再次交给 Hans
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
&gt;&gt; Thanks, Paul.
&gt;&gt;  谢谢 Paul
That was a great demo.
很棒的展示
And that was enhancements in
这就是 UI Image View 的
UIImageView.
优化
We have just looked at seven new
我们已经讲了 tvOS 中的
enhancements in tvOS.
七个优化
But there are many more
但是还有很多 iOS 中的优化
enhancements in iOS that also
现在也可以应用在
apply to tvOS.
tvOS 中
Among them, we think one
其中有一个
deserves a special attention.
特别值得我们的关注
And for that, I'd like to invite
为此  我邀请了媒体框架团队的
Dan from the Media Framework's
Dan 来为我们
Team to tell us all about it.
介绍这个功能
[ Applause ]
[掌声]
&gt;&gt; Thanks, Hans.
&gt;&gt;  谢谢 Hans
Alright, I'm going to take a few
好了  我将花几分钟的时间
minutes to talk about what's new
来讲一讲 tvOS 11 中
in AVKit in tvOS 11.
AVKit 的新功能
AVKit provides standard,
AVkit 为 tvOS 上所有的 app
interactive video playback for
提供标准的
all apps on tvOS.
交互视频回放
Includes, scrubbing, skipping,
包括删除  跳过
scanning, and a variety of
浏览  以及
advanced features like
插页广告  内容建议等
interstitials, and content
先进的
proposals.
功能
Now, we talked about the basics
我们去年讨论了
last year, so if you need to
一些基本的东西  如果
catch up, you can watch the
你们想要了解一下
AVKit on tvOS session from last
可以观看去年 “关于 tvOS 中的 AVKit” 这个
year.
场次
And here we have
我们这里
AVPlayerViewController providing
提供标准视频回放
the standard video playback, in
也就是观看清除数据的
this case, showing scrubbing.
AVP layer View Controller
And advanced features include
还有一些包括
custom content proposals, which
我们去年介绍的定制内容推荐等
we introduced last year.
高级功能
Now, let's talk about what's new
现在  让我们来介绍一下 tvOS 11 的
in tvOS 11.
新功能
When you want to play static
如果你想播放
images, such as a logo or a hint
如图表  提示或者其他
or other information on top of
在你视频之上  但是却在
your video but below the
播放控制器之下的
playback controls, you use the
静态图片  你可以使用
overlay view.
分层视图
In tvOS 11, we're introducing a
在 tvOS 11 中  我们引进了
new layout guide, the Unobscured
一个全新的布局指南
Content Guide, which indicates
Unobscure Content Guide
what portion of the screen you
这个指南会告诉你静态内容
can use for your static content,
在你的屏幕上所占的比重
without overlaying the playback
而不必覆盖播放控制面板
controls or hints.
或提示
Here we see where the unobscured
这就是 Unobscure Content Guide
content guide lays.
所在的外置
As you can see, the hint -- the
我们可以看到
swipe down for info hint is
下滑展示更多信息的提示
above it.
在这个之上
The bottom edge of the layout
而指南的底部
guide goes right against the
正对着
transfer bar.
传输栏
But you do notice that the
但是我们也会注意到
scrubbing thumbnail however is
清除缩略图
not included in that excluded
并不包含在
region.
禁区内
If your content is in the
如果你的内容在
overlay view, it'll be
分层视图中
underneath that scrubbing
它将会出现在
thumbnail.
清除缩略图下
Now, let's talk about the
接下来  让我们介绍一下
transfer bar.
传输栏
Many of you have content, logos,
当传输栏可见时
or what have you, that you want
你们可能想要展示一些内容
to show at the same time that
或图标
Or perhaps you have something
或者当播放控制可见时
like a channel logo that you
你可能希望隐藏
want to hide or get out of the
包括频道图标
way when the playback controls
在内的
are visible.
一些东西
You can do both of these things
通过 Transport Bar Animation Coordinator
with the transfer bar animation
你可以同时实现
coordinator.
这两个功能
To use it, you simply implement
你只需要采用
the delegate method.
Delegate 方法
Player View Controller will
将 Player View Controller 写成
transition to visibility of
“协调完成
transfer bar with coordinator.
传输栏的可见性”
And you add your animations.
加入你的动画
Now, in this example, we are --
在这个例子中
we have a logo image view and
我们可以通过传输栏
we're going to hide it or show
来对我们的图标图像视图
it with the transfer bar.
进行隐藏或展示
Now, by no means are you limited
现在  你不必局限
to this.
于此
You could reverse that
你可以撤销可见性
visibility and hide it instead
把展示改为
of showing it.
隐藏
You could have an additional
你还可以增加动画
animation where your view slides
比如让你的视图
in from the side, for example,
从一边滑过来
or whatever you can -- you want.
或者任何其他你想要的动画
Next, we're giving you greater
接下来  我们将介绍
control over controlling
三个新的委托方法
dismissal with three new
来更好地
delegate methods.
控制撤销
And these are Player View
这里输入播放器视图控制器
Controller should dismiss, will
应该撤销这个指令之后  就会开始
begin dismissal transition, and
撤销转换
did end dismissal transition.
最后终止撤销转换
In many instances, Player View
在很多情况下 Player View
Controller can provide an
Controller 在展示或撤销时
automatic transition when it's
会自动
presented or dismissed.
进行转换
If you simply present or dismiss
如果你只是简单的展示或撤销
it, it can fade in and fade out.
它将淡入和淡出
If you embed the view in your
如果你把这个视图
own view as a thumbnail for
作为缩略图放在你自己的视图中
example, it can automatically
它就会自动缩小
zoom out and automatically zoom
在撤销时
it back when it's dismissed.
又自动变回来
However, in some cases, you may
然而在一些情况下
have some sort of custom
可能有一些自定义展示
presentation where AVKit isn't
AVKit 不能为其
going to be able to provide a
提供合理的转换
reasonable transition and you
这时候你可能就需要
need to do it yourself.
自己动手了
Well, the way you can do that
你操作的方法是
now is, by implementing the
通过运行
Should Dismiss method, and here
Should Dismiss 指令
you would implement your
使你的转换生效
transition and return False to
接着返回为 False
indicate that AVKit should not
来指示 AVKit
provide the standard transition.
不用提供标准的转换
When AVKit does provide the
如果 AVKit 已经提供了转换
transition, it will also call
就会调用
the Will Begin Dismissal and Did
Will Begin Dismissal 和
End Dismissal transition
Did End Dismissal 转换
methods.
这两个方法
So, at the beginning and at the
所以在动画的开端
end of animation.
和结尾
So, you can perform whatever
你可以执行
operations you want to do there,
任何你想要的操作
such as controlling the playback
比如说控制
rate for example.
回放速度
The info views, are shown when
当视频回放时
the user swipes down during
用户可以通过下滑
video playback.
看到信息视图
And the standard info views
标准的信息视图会提供
provide a variety of interesting
包括元数据
things, including metadata,
导航标 字幕控制
navigation markers, subtitle
以及音频选择等信息
controls, and audio options, as
你们现在所看到的
you can see here.
有趣的东西
Now, a lot of you would like to
你们很多人现在可能
have your own controls here.
想要在这里加入你们自己的操纵模块
And so, I'm pleased to announce
所以 我很高兴地告诉大家
that we are introducing custom
我们现在可以
info views.
自定义信息视图
In tvOS 11, you can provide a
在 tvOS 11 中
custom info view as you can see
你可以像这个例子中所呈现的一样
in this example.
提供一个自定义信息视图
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
So, all you need to do is create
你们所需要的
your own UIView Controller.
只是创造你们自己的 UI View Controller
You need determine the contents
你需要决定它的
of it.
内容
Set the custom Info View
为你的 Player View Controller
Controller Property of your
设置自定义的 Info View Controller
Player View Controller, and
性能
that's it.
就这么简单
Now, we ask that you keep your
你们需要将风格
style consistent with the other
与其他的信息视图
info views so that the user
统一
won't feel out of place or
这样用户才不会感到违和
confused.
或者困惑
And to that end, we have some
对于这一点  我们有几个
guidelines.
建议
So, first, use the standard font
首先  使用标准的字体
styles.
风格
Second, keep your view
第二  保持你的视图背景
background transparent so that
为透明色
the effect's view will show
这样效果的视图就能
through.
显示出来
You can indicate the desired
你可以指示
height of your info view, using
你信息视图的预期高度
auto layout, which is the best
而最好的方法就是使用
way to do it.
自动布局
But if you prefer, you can
不过如果你喜欢的话
override Preferred Content Size
也可以在视图控制器上
on your View Controller instead.
使用内容尺寸优先选项
And regardless of which of those
除了这些之外
you use, keep your content to no
你的内容也不能
more than half of the height of
超过屏幕高度的一半
the screen because you don't get
因为你并不需要
to use the entire screen.
使用整个屏幕
And as for controls, while, you
你还可以使用任何
can use whatever you want, we
你想要的控件
would recommend that you avoid
不过我们建议你不要使用
things like text fields and
诸如文本框
buttons, which feel out of
还有按钮
place, and instead prefer things
这些具有违和感的东西
like collection and table views.
最好使用集合或者图表视图
Alright, finally, I'd like to
好了  最后我想来讲一下
talk about Live Streams.
直播流媒体
We're adding four new metadata
在 tvOS 11 中  我们增加了
identifiers in tvOS 11 that lets
四个新的元数据标识符
you specify the starting date
你可以在你的直播
and ending date of your live
或事件流中指定
stream or your event stream.
开始和结束的时间
Now, as an example, one example
举个例子
where you want to use the exact
有个节目你想要
end date, would be something
使用确切的结束日期
like a traditional broadcast
和传统的播放流媒体一样
stream, where you have a
你可能需要把
continuous live stream that's
直播流媒体按照
broken up into scheduled blocks
30分钟或者60分钟的容量
of 30 minutes or 60 minutes.
分成好几部分
And in that case, you can use
在那种情况下
the exact start and exact end
你就可以使用明确的开始和结束
dates to indicate what part of
时间来指明
that program you're watching
你现在正在收看的节目
right now.
属于哪个部分
How about the approximate end
那么近似结束时间
date?
又是怎么样的呢
Well, the easiest example there
最简单的例子就是
would something like a sporting
比如说有一个
event where you know for example
体育比赛
that the game will probably last
你知道它可能会进行三个小时
about three hours, but you
但是你实在不知道
really have no idea up front how
它实际会
long it's going to go.
进行多久
It could end sooner.
它可能结束地早
It could end later.
可能结束地晚
And in that case, you use an
在这种情况下  你就可以使用
approximate end date.
近似结束时间
In either case, the transfer of
在这些情况中
our timescale will reflect these
时标的变化都会显示
dates.
这些时间
So, it will either reflect more
它要么显示更多时间
time or less time.
要么显示更少时间
When you provide exact values,
当你提供具体数值时
those are displayed on the
在传输栏上会展示
transfer bar with a clock time
一个时钟的时间
and approximate values are not
而近似数值则不会显示
shown, so that these are --
所以这样就
isn't misled into thinking it's
不会误导用户
going to end precisely at the
节目会正好在结束时间
end time.
结束
And this helps to orient the
这也会帮助用户
user to where they are in your
了解他们观看节目的
program.
进度
How much they've missed, how
他们错过了多少
much they should expect to have
节目还会持续
before the program is over.
多长时间
So, let's just to visualize
形象一点来说
that, this -- in the case where
在你有直播流的
you have a live stream, and you
情况下
haven't specified either a start
你没有指定开始和结束时间
or an end date, you get the
那么一切都是
default or legacy behavior.
默认或遗留状态
Now in the past, this differs a
这与我们在
little bit from what we did in
tvOS 10 中有点不太一样
tvOS 10, because in the past, we
因为在过去
showed the start and the end
我们会显示开始和结束
times.
时间
We no longer do that because
我们不再这样做了
they're both approximate.
因为它们都是近似值
But you would have a 30-minute
但是你可以有一个 30 分钟的
window.
窗口
So, in this example, it would
在这个例子中
run from 11 to 11:30, and so the
它会从 11 点播放到 11:30
11:28 mark is near the end.
所以 11:28 这个标记接近结束时间
However, now that's fine if your
如果你的节目是从 11 点
program actually from 11 to
播放到 11 点半
11:30, but what if it doesn't?
那么一切正常  但是如果不是呢
What if it's -- you're in the
如果你正在
middle of a three-hour baseball
观看一个三小时的
game or something?
棒球赛或者其他好看的节目呢
Well, here's an example with
好了  现在有一个
exact start and end dates, in
拥有确切开始和结束时间的例子
this case, 10 o'clock to 1
在这个例子中  节目从 10 点播放到 13 点
o'clock, 11:28 you see is now
你可以看到 11:28 大致在
roughly in the middle, and the
中间位置
scale has been adjusted.
而比例也相应进行了调整
And of course, we can set an
当然了  我们可以
approximate end date instead and
设置一个近似的结束日期
that just makes the end time
这样结束的时间就会
disappear.
消失不见
But the scale remains the same.
不过它的比例还是一样的
So, let's look briefly at the
现在我们来简单看看
code for this.
它的代码
If you've seen last year's
如果你看了去年的会议
session, the new metadata item
那么这个新的元数据项目
helper function will look
助手功能可能对你来说
familiar.
比较熟悉
All we're going to do is we're
我们要做的就是
going to create our start dates.
创造我们的开始时间
We're going to create a metadata
我们将为之创造一个
item for it.
元数据项目
We're going to do the same thing
对于结束时间也需要
for our end date.
重复此操作
And finally, we're going to add
最终  我们将为
our two metadata items to our
我们的播放器项目
player item, to the external
增加两个元数据项目
metadata property.
以此获得外部元数据性能
Alright, now we're going to try
好了  现在我们来看一个
a brief demo.
简单的展示
I've got a few things I can show
我现在只能展示少数几个
here.
东西
First, here's our Unobscured
首先  这是我们的
Content Guide.
Unobscured Content Guide
And, if we let it fade out, it
如果我们让它淡出
fades with it, because I'm using
它会这样消失
the transfer bar animation
因为我正在使用传输栏
coordinator.
动画协调器
So, it fades out quickly.
所以  它消失得非常快
I feel like I should wave at
我感觉我应该向自己
myself.
挥挥手
And here we have a custom info
这些就是自定义的信息
view.
视图
As we saw earlier, and we can
这些是我们之前看过的
switch it from -- to -- let's
我们可以来回转换
put it on exact dates.
选中“确切时间”
And there we go.
好了
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
The good news is that the
好消息是这个会议
session is not in fact going
并不会持续
three hours.
三个小时
I just did that because if I set
我这样设置是因为
the actual end time, the current
如果我设置了真实的结束时间
time would be too close to the
现在的时间和结束时间会太接近
end time and they would -- the
这样的话
event time would be hidden
事件时间将被隐藏
because they'd be overlapping
因为它们会相互
otherwise.
重叠
But, here's another look at that
再来看一下我们的
code.
代码
People viewing this at home
人们在家里
later are going to be very
看到你刚刚突然的出现
confused that you just dropped
都会感到困惑
in right now, because the audio
因为音轨
track seems a little bit off.
似乎有点脱离视频
Alright, and that's our demo.
好了  这就是我们的展示
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
Back to the slides.
回到我们的幻灯片
Alright, so that's -- we've
我们介绍了
talked about several new
AVKit 中的
features in AVKit, and there are
几个新性能
a couple more that I haven't
但是还有很多
talked about, but these are the
我没有讲到  不过我讲的
most important ones.
都是其中最重要的
For more information about using
想要了解更多在 tvOS 中
AVKit on tvOS, see last year's
使用 AVKit 的信息  可以观看
session.
去年的会议
And you can also join us in the
同时还可以在这场会议结束后的 11 点
AVKit lab, shortly after this
到1点前
session at 11, until 1, in Tech
在 tech lab F 中
Lab F.
加入 AVKit lab
And bring us your questions.
并告诉我们你的问题
And now, I'd like to introduce
现在  我想有请
Marshall to the stage to talk
Marshall 上台
about View Controller
来介绍 View Controller 的
enhancements.
优化
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
&gt;&gt; Thank you, Dan.
&gt;&gt;  谢谢 Dan
My name is Marshall, and today
我是 Marshall  今天
I'm going to talk about View
我将介绍
Controller Enhancements in tvOS
tvOS 11中 view controller 的
11.
优化
Let's dive right in.
我们直接开始吧
First, we're going to take a
首先  我们来看一看
look at mobile presentations.
模态演示
If you've ever used the UI Alert
如果你曾经使用过 UI Alert Controller
Controller or put your Apple TV
或者曾将你的 Apple TV 设成睡眠状态
to sleep, you might recognize
你可能会对这个转换
this transition where we
比较熟悉
progressively blur the content
我们会逐渐将内容模糊
and animate in the View
并在 View Controller 中
Controller.
使用动画
Well, starting in tvOS 11, you
在 tvOS 11 中
can now do that in your own
你可以在自己的应用中
applications, using the new UI
使用这个名为
Multi-Presentation Style called,
Blur Over Full Screen 的
.blurOverFullScreen.
模态演示风格
This will progressively blur the
它将把展示的视图控制器中的
content of the presenting view
内容逐渐变模糊
controller, and it uses the same
这个所使用的
timings in the animations that
是和 UI Alert Controller 中一样的
UI Alert Controller does.
动画和定时器
Implementing this is easy.
设置这个也很简单
You set the mobile presentation
将模块演示风格
style to blur over full screen,
设置为全屏模糊
and present your view
将你的视图控制器
controller, like you normally
设置的和平常
would.
一样
Next, we're going to talk about
接下来  我们要讨论一些优化
some enhancements, the UI Split
那就是 UI Split
View Controller.
View Controller
If you've used a split view
如果你曾经在应用中
controller in your application
使用过分屏视图控制器
before, then you know that the
那你应该知道
master view controller's on the
主控制器在左边
left, and the detailed view
详细控制器
controller's on the right.
则在右边
Well, starting in tvOS 11, we
在 tvOS 11 中
now have a new property that
我们有一个新的性能
will allow you to swap the
可以让你改变
layout.
这个布局
In order to support this, we
为了支撑这个功能
have a new enum called UI Split
我们有一个拥有
View Controller Primary Edge
Leading 和 trailing 两个数值的
with two values, leading and
UI Split View Controller
trailing.
Primary Edge 的新枚举
And then, a property that you
还有一个你可以设置 primary edge 的
can set the primary edge.
性能
Now, these names are important
这些名词现在很重要
because as we heard, tvOS now
因为我们刚刚也听到了
supports RTL languages.
tvOS 现在支持 RTL 语言了
So, in this case, if you have a
所以  在这种情况下
left to right language and use
如果你使用了从左至右的语言
leading, the master view
并且使用 leading
controller will be on the left,
那么主控制器就会在左边
and trailing the master view
而如果使用 trailing
controller, would on the right.
主控制器则会在右边
But in RTL languages, those will
不过在 RTL 语言中
be mirrored, so the master would
这一切就反过来了
be on the right, and for
主控制器会在右边
trailing, it will be on the
对 trailing 来说
left.
则是左边
Last year, we announced a new
去年 我们宣布将使用
use facing feature where users
一个功能让
can change their system
用户可以把系统外观
appearance to dark.
调暗
And this allows a great
这样如果用户的 Apple TV
experience when their Apple TV's
是在影音室内
in a movie room or perhaps for
或者用户想在晚上使用它
use at night.
那他们将有更好的体验
Well, starting this year, we
今年开始
have another mode which we call
我们有另一个名为自动化的
automatic.
模式
And what this will do, is it
它的功能就是
will automatically change the
根据它所处的位置
user's system appearance to dark
将用户的系统外观
at night, and light during the
在晚上时自动调暗
day, based on their current
在白天时则自动
location.
调亮
Now, it's more important than
为了提供最优质的用户体验
ever to make sure apps adopt the
保证 app 能调节明暗
light and dark appearance to
比以往来说要更
offer the best user experience.
重要
In order to support this, we've
为了支撑该功能
added some new APIs.
我们增加了一些新的 API
First, let's take a look at Top
首先  我们来看一下
Shelf.
Top Shelf
If you've provided a Top Shelf
如果你曾经提供过 Top shelf extension
extension, you know you can
那你应该知道
provide an image URL to provide
你可以通过提供图片网址
images up in the Top Shelf.
把图片放在 top shelf 上
Now, we are allowing a new API
我们现在有新的 API
to provide a dark image asset as
可以提供一个暗图
well, and the system will
系统会根据系统外观
automatically choose the correct
自动选择
asset to show, based on the
合适的素材
system appearance.
来展示
So, if you've looked into this
如果你曾经浏览过这些
before, you have then a TV
你会有一个 TV 内容条目
content item and then set the
然后是设置图像
image URL.
URL
Starting in tvOS 11, you can now
在 tvOS 11 中 你可以
call Set Image URL for traits
将 Set Image URL 设为 for traits
and provide a light and dark
并分别提供一个 light trait 和
trait to provide those image
dark trait 来创作
assets.
图片素材
If you'd like to still use the
如果你想使用相同的图片
same image, then you can just
你可以在这些方法调用中
provide the same image URL to
提供相同的
both these method calls.
图像地址
Finally, today, we're going to
最后 我们将介绍
talk about how you can adapt
如何使你的 app 外观
your app's appearance to your
融合到
content.
内容中
We do this in our apps, such as
我们的 app 就做到了这一点
our movies where if a movie has
比如说在我们的电影中 如果
artwork that's light, we'll show
有一个电影插图是亮色的
appropriate controls, and if
我们就会展示合适的控件
it's dark, we'll also show
如果插图是暗色的
controls that look best on that.
我们也会展示看上去最合适的控件
Well, in order to make this
为了让开发者
easier for developers, we have a
更简单地实现这个性能
new property on UI View
我们在 UI View Controller 中
Controller, called Preferred
有一个名为 Preferred
User Interface Style.
User Interface Style 的新性能
If you've ever used preferred
如果你们曾经使用
status bar style, then this
preferred status bar style
might look familiar to you.
这个对你们来说可能比较眼熟
What it lets you do is specify a
它的作用是
specific UI User Interface
在视图控制器上
Style, on your view controller,
指定特定的 UI User Interface Style
which will customize the
它会通过更新
appearance by updating the trait
特征集合和系统墙纸
collection, and update the
来自定义
system wallpaper.
外观
Let's take a look at what this
我们来看看最终的
looks like.
效果
Here, I've got a Tab-R
我有一个 Tab—R 控制器
controller, where the first view
这里第一个视图控制器
controller specifies a preferred
指定的是偏好
style of light, and the second
亮色风格
view controller specifies a
第二个则指定的
preferred style dark.
是偏好暗色风格
When we switch tabs, we see that
当我们转换标签时
the application's trait
可以看到
collection automatically get
应用的特征集合
updated, as does the system
和系统墙纸
wallpaper.
都自动更新了
So, we've added three new API
所以  我们有三个新的 API 方法
method for you to implement this
可以让各位把其应用在
in your own apps.
自己的 app 中
First, we have a read only
首先  在你们的视图控制器中
property, called Preferred User
改写一个名为
Interface Style that you
优先用户界面风格
override in your View
的
Controller.
只读性能
Here you can provide UI User
在这里  你可以将用户
Interfaced Style, light, dark,
界面风格设为浅黑色
or unspecified, which means
或者未定义
follow the system style.
也就是遵循系统风格
For most people, this is
对于大多数人来说
probably enough to handle what
这也许就能满足他们的
you want.
需要
But if you're using custom view
不过如果你使用的是
controllers, and using Child
自定义视图控制器
View Controller Containment,
并使用了包含子视图控制器
there's two more methods that
这里有两个方法
you're going to want to use.
你可以使用
First, the Child View Controller
第一个就是用以用户界面风格设置
For User Interface Style, let's
的子视图控制器
you delegate that decision to
你可以将这个决定委托给
review controller.
review controller
In the case of tab bar
在选项栏控制器中
controller, the current selected
目前选择的
tab bar view controller -- or
选项栏视图控制器
the current selected View
或者目前选择的视图控制器
Controller, gets returned here.
会在这里回归
And then, when that change
然后 当发生变化时
occurs, you need to call Set
你需要调用 Set
Needs User Interface Appearance
需要用户界面外观
Update.
升级
This lets the system know that a
这会告知系统
change occurred and we can
有变化发生
refigure out what the preferred
我们会重新找到
style's going to be for your
你应用的偏好风格
application.
是什么
So, those are our View
这就是我们今天要讲的
Controller Enhancements today.
视图控制器的优化
Let's take a look and see what
我们可以最后来看看
we covered.
今天所讲的内容
First, we learned that on-demand
首先  我们认识到
resources bundle size have been
ODR bundle 的最大值
increased from 200 megabytes to
从 200MB 上升到
4 gigabytes that allow you to
4GB 从而让你在
package more content on the
安装应用时
application install.
可以包含更多的内容
We learned that tvOS now
我们了解到 tvOS
supports RTL languages, so make
现在支持 RTL 语言
sure to use the tools we provide
所以请记得使用
to test your layouts for those
我们为那些语言设计的
languages.
测试你们布局的工具
We learned about new ways to do
我们还了解了一些新方法
work in the background to make
可以在用户使用
sure that your content's always
你们的应用时
updated and ready for the user
在后台运作
when they launch your
让内容时刻
application.
保持更新
We talked about new AVKit
我们还讨论了包括
enhancements including, the
定制信息视图在内的
custom info views.
新的 AVKit 优化
We also saw a new API on Image
我们同时还看到了
Views, so you can make your
Image View 上新的 API
content more interactive for the
可以让你的内容对用户来说
user.
更有交互性
And finally, we talked about how
最后  我们还讨论了
to adapt your content, your
如何使用你偏好的
application's appearance to your
用户界面风格
content, using preferred user
将你的内容和应用外观
interface style.
适用到你的内容中去
If you'd like any more
如果你想要了解
information, please develop --
更多资讯
please visit
请登录
developer.apple.com.
developer.apple.com
If you want to expand on any of
如果你想要了解关于这些话题的
the topics we have, we have a
更详细的内容
lot of related sessions,
我们还有很多包括
including a few videos this
今年的一些视频的
year.
相关场次
Thank you for coming and I hope
感谢你们的聆听
you enjoy the rest of the
希望你们能在
conference.
接下来的会议度过愉快的时光
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]